CRUSADE IN PERU WITH T.B. JOSHUA - Monumental Stadium, Lima, Peru
Prophet T.B. Joshua Arrives In The Nation Of Peru
"Prophet T.B. Joshua, welcome to Peru!"
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Arrival In The Nation Of Peru
As Prophet T.B Joshua arrives late Wednesday night at the Jorge Chavez International Airport in the nation of Peru,
he is warmly received by the thronging crowd, comprising of government officials,
Christian leaders and army generals, among others.
The citizens of Peru are elated by what God Almighty is about to do in their nation
through God's anointed servant, Prophet T.B Joshua.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Arrival In The Nation Of Peru
Having been ushered through the bustling crowd,
Prophet T.B Joshua then makes his way to the vehicle,
which will convey him to his place of residence;
throughout the period of his stay in Peru.
The nation of Peru certainly has a lot to look forward to,
going by the track record of how God has used Prophet T.B Joshua,
impacting nations around the world.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Arrival In The Nation Of Peru
Peruvians and people from other countries express their joy and wave excitedly,
believing that with this historic visit of Prophet T. B Joshua,
their nation will never remain the same again.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's Arrival In The Nation Of Peru
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.